<schemalist>
	<schema id="org.gnome.desk-changer" path="/org/gnome/desk-changer/">
		<key name="auto-rotate" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<description>
				When enabled, this will cause the extension to automatically change the wallpaper as soon as a new
				profile is loaded into the wallpapers component.
			</description>
			<summary>Automatically change the wallpaper when a new profile is loaded</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="current-profile" type="s">
			<default>"default"</default>
			<description>
				This holds the name of the currently selected profile. Changing this will trigger the wallpaper
				component to load the new profile automatically.
			</description>
			<summary>Current profile name</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="interval" type="i">
			<default>300</default>
			<description>
				This is the number of seconds that will be scheduled with the timer if interval changing of the
				wallpapers is enabled
			</description>
			<summary>Timer length for interval (in seconds)</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="lock-disables-timer" type="b">
			<default>false</default>
			<description>
				When the screen is locked, the extension itself is disabled because of how gnome-shell works. This
				setting ensures the timer stays running during that time.
			</description>
			<summary>Locking the screen disables the timer</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="notifications" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<description>
				If enabled the extension will show notifications when the profile is switched to a different profile
				and when the wallpaper is switched to a different wallpaper, weather it was automatically or manually.
			</description>
			<summary>Display notifications for events in the extension</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="profiles" type="s">
			<default>'{"default": [["file:///usr/share/backgrounds/gnome", true]]}'</default>
			<description>
				This is where all of the profiles are stored for the wallpapers. This setting will be automatically
				be JSON encoded when it is set and it will be parsed when it is gotten.
			</description>
			<summary>JSON encoded list of profiles</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="random" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<description>
				If enabled the wallpaper component will randomly choose wallpapers from the available files on the
				current profile. If it is disabled the wallpapers will be chosen in order they are loaded.
			</description>
			<summary>Randomly select the next wallpaper</summary>
		</key>
		<key name="timer-enabled" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<description>
				If the timer is enabled it will be added to the main loop with the interval specified by the interval
				setting. Once the timer callback is triggered the wallpaper will be changed to the next wallpaper
				available.
			</description>
			<summary>Enable the timer</summary>
		</key>
	</schema>
</schemalist>
